#### Contact

mommanurseshark@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/shelley-lee-dnp-rnc-nic-cmsrn-cphrm-cpso-bc-8a92173a (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Clinical Research NRP Hospitals

### Certifications

Nursing Professional Development Certified Professional Healthcare Risk Manager

Lean Six Sigma Green Belt Certification

Certified Patient Safety Offiicer

# Shelley Lee, DNP, RNC-NIC, CMSRN, CPHRM, CPSO, BC

Risk Manager Patient Safety Officer

Nashville, Tennessee

## Summary

Experienced Risk Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Nursing Education, Nursing Documentation, Instructional Design, NRP Instruction, and Neonatal Nursing. Strong nursing/ risk professional with a Doctor of Nursing Practice focused in Healthcare Systems Leadership from Chamberlain College of Nursing.

## Experience

Nashville General Hospital 3 years 1 month

Risk Manager March 2018 - Present (2 years 4 months) Greater Nashville Area, TN

Director of Nursing June 2017 - March 2018 (10 months) Nashville, TN

Via Christi Health Nursing Practice Specialist August 2010 - May 2017 (6 years 10 months) Wichita. KS

Primary responsibilities:

Onboarding New Nursing Staff and Assistive Staff
Nursing Continuing Education Providership Coordinator
Learning Management System Administration
High Reliability Organization Trainer
RN Nurse Residency
Inter-professional Simulation
Competency Development
Program Development

Conference Planning

Career Advising

Performance Coaching

**Professional Development Consultation** 

Nursing House Supervisor August 2010- March 2011

**Newman University** 

Assistant Professor of Nursing

August 2008 - July 2010 (2 years)

Taught Fundamentals of Nursing Didactic Content, Nursing Skills Lab, and

Foundations of Nursing Clinical.

Chairman of three courses.

Developed detailed, multi-sensory learning experiences for students in nursing skills lab.

Wrote simulation scenarios.

Developed tools for learning.

Developed evaluation rubrics.

Assisted with curricular planning.

Advised students related to career planning and academic goals.

Mount Clemens Regional Medical Center

Staff Nurse

October 1996 - September 2007 (11 years)

Mount Clemens, MI

Special Care Nursery

Family Birthing Center

St. Clair County Community College

Adjunct Nursing Faculty

in ADN and LPN programs.

2001 - 2007 (6 years)

Taught Fundamentals of Nursing, Medical Surgical Nursing I, Medical Surgical Nursing II, Pediatric Nursing, Obstetric Nursing, and Surgical Nursing Clinicals

Crittenton Hospital Medical Center

Staff Nurse

August 1998 - July 2003 (5 years)

Rochester, MI

Provided patient centered care for post partum mothers and infants.

Provided patient centered care for gyn surgical patients.

Provided pfamily centered care for acutely ill neonates in Special Care Nursery.

Taught CPR and NRP to nursing and respiratory care staff.

Coordinated NRP for three departments.

Developed continuing education modules for staff.

### Education

Chamberlain College of Nursing

Doctor of Nursing Practice, Healthcare Systems Leadership · (2014 - 2016)

Michigan State University

MSN, Nursing · (2005 - 2008)

Graceland University

BSN, Nursing · (1996 - 2003)

Macomb Community College

AAS, Nursing · (1992 - 1994)

Saginaw Valley State University

BS, Biology · (1987 - 1990)